[GamerHash AI
    
    AI and GPU/CPU earning](https://gamerhash.com/en/app-download)
    
    N

    [GamerHash Miner
    
    Mining with GPU/CPU](https://gamerhash.com/en/app-download)

    [GamerHash Mobile
    
    Wallet, store and AI Chat](https://gamerhash.com/en/app-download)

* [](javascript:void(null);)

    Don't have an account?

    or

Data safety policy
==================

01

##### GENERAL PROVISIONS

1. The Privacy Policy informs about the purposes, legal bases, and methods of processing personal data, as well as the rights of users directly related to the processing of personal data of users of the GamerHash Portal (hereinafter: Portal) by its operator, C-Axe Sp. z o.o. with its registered office in Poznań.
2. The administrator of users' personal data is C-Axe Sp. z o.o. with its registered office in Poznań (60-771), at ul. Marii Konopnickiej 16/3A (hereinafter: C-Axe), registered in the National Court Register under the number: 0000702796, email address: [\[email protected\]](https://gamerhash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
3. C-Axe processes personal data in accordance with the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation) (hereinafter: GDPR).
4. Processing of personal data includes all activities performed on personal data, in particular their collection, recording, storage, retrieval, viewing, use, transmission, erasure, or destruction.

02

##### SCOPE, PURPOSE, AND LEGAL BASIS OF DATA PROCESSING

1. CoinAxe processes your personal data in the following scope:

1. Username, email address, and password for the purpose of user account registration,
2. Username, email address, and password for the purpose of user account registration, profile picture including avatar, for account registration using an external provider such as Facebook,
3. Username, email address, information regarding the time and frequency of logging into the Portal, type of browser used by the User, device IP address used for logging in, type and parameters of the device on which the Application is installed, data related to cryptocurrency exchange transactions to Bitcoin, withdrawal of Bitcoin, or conversion of Bitcoin, carried out under the conditions specified in the Portal's Regulations, for the purpose of maintaining the user account and providing services in accordance with the provisions of the Regulations (including the execution of transactions: exchange of cryptocurrency for Bitcoin, withdrawal of Bitcoin, conversion of Bitcoin into products offered on the Portal),
4. Email address/mailing address to provide a response to a question directed by the User to C-Axe via electronic message or in the form of traditional correspondence,
5. Username, email address, for the purpose of registration, organization, and resolution of contests,
6. Email address for conducting marketing activities, including sending information about discounts, promotions, organized contests, and GamerHash updates,
7. Data collected in cookie files, including information about the time and frequency of logging into the Portal, the type of browser used by the User, the IP address of the device from which the login occurred, the type and parameters of the device on which the Application was installed, for the purpose of personalizing displayed content, developing offered products and services, and compiling anonymous statistics.

3. Personal data is processed for the purpose of registering the User and subsequent maintenance of the User's account, including transaction history, carrying out transactions: exchanging Cryptocurrency for Bitcoin, withdrawing Bitcoin, exchanging Bitcoin for products offered on the Portal, to pursue the legitimate interests of C-Axe, i.e., building the image of C-Axe through contact with the User (User inquiries regarding Portal functionality, reporting technical issues, conducting User surveys, even after the provision of services (account closure), and the ability to demonstrate the correctness of transaction processing). In case the User provides separate consent, the data may also be processed for marketing purposes, sending commercial offers, and organizing and resolving contests.
4. The legal basis for processing personal data is as follows:

1. The legal basis for processing personal data is the user's consent, specifically for marketing activities, sending commercial offers, organizing and resolving contests, and using Cookies and other analytical tools (Article 6(1)(a) of the General Data Protection Regulation - RODO).
2. The processing of personal data is based on the execution of a contract, specifically concerning the registration and subsequent maintenance of the account, including the transaction history of exchanging cryptocurrency for Bitcoin, withdrawing Bitcoin cryptocurrency, exchanging Bitcoin cryptocurrency for products offered on the Portal (Article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation - RODO)
3. Legitimate interest of C-Axe includes building the image of C-Axe through contact with the User (responding to User inquiries), improving the quality of services based on the feedback and opinions of Users and former Users, and demonstrating the correctness of transaction execution (Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation - RODO).
4. Fulfillment of legal obligations imposed on C-Axe, in particular settling contests and providing personal data along with information about their processing to the relevant state authorities, including tax and fiscal authorities (Article 6(1)(c) of the General Data Protection Regulation - RODO).
5. Pursuing or securing claims based on Article 6(1)(f) of the General Data Protection Regulation (RODO).

6. Personal data processed for the purpose of executing contracts and participating in contests will be processed for the duration of their validity and then for the period necessary to defend against potential claims by the Portal User. Personal data processed for marketing purposes, sending commercial offers, and participating in contests will be processed until the consent is withdrawn.
7. Personal data of individuals who registered an account but did not use its functionality before deleting the account are stored for 6 months from the date of deletion.
8. Personal data collected for the purpose of maintaining contact are stored for a period of 6 months, calculated from the date of the last contact.
9. Information collected through cookies and similar technologies is processed for the duration specified in the Cookies Policy.
10. Personal data may be disclosed to entities authorized to receive them under applicable law, including relevant judicial authorities. Personal data may be transferred to entities cooperating with the Administrator, including but not limited to programmers, analysts, entities offering communication tools, and entities offering marketing tools.
11. Personal data of Users will be transferred outside the European Economic Area, i.e., to the United States of America, as part of the transfer of personal data to recipients mentioned in point 6. The transfer of data is carried out under standard contractual clauses, meaning that the Recipients provide an adequate level of protection for the transferred personal data, particularly by applying appropriate technical and organizational measures.
12. Providing personal data by the User is voluntary, but failure to provide them will make it impossible to register and maintain the User's account, execute transactions, send marketing information and commercial offers, participate in contests, and receive feedback from C-Axe. Providing personal data for settlement of contests is mandatory and follows from the provisions of applicable law.

03

##### USERS' RIGHTS RELATED TO PERSONAL DATA PROCESSING

1. The user has the right to:

1. access their data,
2. rectify personal data,
3. erase data,
4. restrict processing,
5. object to processing,
6. data portability, with the reservation that the right to data portability applies only to data processed in an automated manner.

3. In cases where the legal basis for processing the user's personal data is their consent, the user may withdraw consent at any time without affecting the processing carried out before the withdrawal.
4. C-Axe may refuse to comply with a request to erase data in cases provided for by law, particularly when further processing is necessary to fulfill a legal obligation requiring processing under Union or national law or for the purpose of establishing, pursuing, or defending claims. Data deletion is not possible, especially if the person remains a registered user of the Portal and still wants to use its functionalities.
5. The user can delete their account at any time, but deleting the account does not equate to deleting the data. In the case of account deletion, C-Axe processes personal data for the next 6 years from the date of deletion, to fulfill legal obligations and potential claims settlement or defense. This applies to users who have, among other things, exchanged cryptocurrencies.
6. C-Axe promptly removes the data of users who registered an account but did not use any of its functionalities, as well as individuals who were not users of the service but contacted C-Axe.
7. In the event of a breach of the user's personal data, the user has the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority.
8. Requests to exercise the rights mentioned in points 1-2 above should be sent by the user to the email address: [\[email protected\]](https://gamerhash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

04

##### PRINCIPLES OF PROCESSING PERSONAL DATA

1. The processing of user data is carried out in accordance with the principles of adequacy, purposefulness, and minimization, to the extent necessary for the proper functioning of the Portal and Application, including enhancing their functionality, the proper execution of the mutual agreement between the User and C-Axe in connection with downloading the Application, the proper execution of cryptocurrency exchange transactions for Bitcoin, cryptocurrency withdrawal transactions, or cryptocurrency exchange transactions, and for the proper protection of the rights and interests of C-Axe and Users.
2. C-Axe takes the utmost care to ensure that the processed data is substantively correct and up-to-date. The substantive correctness and currency of data depend to a large extent on the Users. Users will promptly inform C-Axe of any changes to their data.
3. The processing of user data is carried out with the utmost care to maintain their security, while observing appropriate organizational and technical measures. In connection with the development of modern technologies and the possibility of third parties taking actions contrary to the law and infringing on the interests of Users, ensuring complete security, inviolability, and integrity of data is not possible. Users are aware of this risk and accept it.
4. Personal data is processed automatically, using C-Axe software. Automatic processing is carried out to optimize the results of obtaining cryptocurrencies by the Device on which the Application is installed.

05

##### CONTACT

The appropriate contact for all matters related to user data, including the provisions of the Privacy Policy, is the email inbox: [\[email protected\]](https://gamerhash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

06

##### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGE

1. C-Axe has the right to change the Privacy Policy, with the provision that any changes will be implemented with the utmost care to maintain the security of processed personal data. This includes the use of technical and organizational safeguards adequate to the security threats identified by C-Axe.
2. Information about changes to the Privacy Policy will be provided to the user during the first login after the Privacy Policy change, in the form of a notification.
3. The user is obligated to review the updated Privacy Policy. Acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy is a condition for continued use of the account on the portal. In case of non-acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy, the user's account will be deleted.

#### COOKIE POLICY GAMERHASH.COM

01

##### COOKIE FILES

1. The Cookies Policy provides information on the principles of using cookies on the GamerHash Portal (hereinafter: the Portal) by its operator C-Axe Sp. z o.o. (hereinafter: C-Axe) with its registered office in Poznań.
2. The administrator of Users' personal data is C-Axe Spółka z ograniczoną odpowiedzialnością with its registered office in Poznań (60-771), at ul. Marii Konopnickiej 16/3A (hereinafter: C-Axe), registered in the National Court Register under the number: 0000702796, email address: [\[email protected\]](https://gamerhash.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) .
3. C-Axe processes personal data in accordance with the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation) (hereinafter: GDPR).
4. Cookies are computer data, in particular text files, stored on Users' devices and intended for using websites. These files allow recognizing the user's device and displaying the website adapted to their individual preferences. The default parameters of Cookies allow the information contained in them to be read only by the server that created them. Cookies usually contain the name of the website from which they originate, the time of storing them on the end device, and a unique number.
5. Cookies are used to adapt the content of the website to the User's preferences and its optimization. In addition, Cookies are used to create anonymous, aggregate statistics, allowing to check how the User uses the website, which provides the opportunity to improve the content and structure of the Portal, excluding personal identification of the User.
6. Software used to browse websites by default allows placing Cookies on the end device. These settings can be changed to block automatic handling of Cookies in the web browser settings or to inform about their every transmission to the User's device. Detailed information on the possibilities and methods of handling Cookies is available in the software settings (web browser). Limiting the use of Cookies may affect some functionalities available on the website.

02

##### TYPES OF COOKIES AND STORAGE TIME

1. Taking into account the purpose of collecting cookies, the following types are distinguished:
    1. essential: necessary for the proper functioning of the service – files processed based on the legitimate interest of the administrator (Art. 6(1)(f) of the GDPR);
        
        | name | lifespan | provider |
        | --- | --- | --- |
        | rc::a | persistant | google.com |
        | rc::c | sesyjne | google.com |
        | XSRF-TOKEN | 1 day | gamerhash.com |
        
    2. Statistical: these allow us to analyze website traffic, understand our users' preferences, analyze their behavior on the site, and enable interactions with external networks and platforms – files processed based on the user's voluntary consent (Article 6(1)(a) of the GDPR);
        
        | name | lifespan | provider |
        | --- | --- | --- |
        | \_clck | 1 year | gamerhash.com |
        | \_clsk | 1 day | gamerhash.com |
        | \_cltk | secesion | gamerhash.com |
        | \_ga | 399 days | gamerhash.com |
        | \_ga\_# | 399 days | gamerhash.com |
        | \_gat | 1 day | gamerhash.com |
        | \_gid | 1 day | gamerhash.com |
        | CLID | 1 year | clarity.ms |
        
    3. Marketing: these allow us to tailor displayed ads and content to our users' preferences and conduct personalized marketing campaigns – files processed based on the user's voluntary consent (Article 6(1)(a) of the GDPR);
        
        | name | lifespan | provider |
        | --- | --- | --- |
        | \_fbp | 3 months | gamerhash.com |
        | ANONCHK | 1 day | c.clarity.ms |
        | MUID | 1 year | clarity.ms |
        | SM  | secesion | c.clarity.ms |
        | smartlook\_setup\_retry\_after | persistent | gamerhash.com |
        | smartlook\_setup\_retry\_after\_reason | persistent | gamerhash.com |
        | SRM\_B | 1 year | bing.com |
        
    4. unclassified.
        
        | name | lifespan | provider |
        | --- | --- | --- |
        | gamerhash\_session | 1 day | gamerhash.com |

03

##### DETAILED INFORMATION

1. The gamerhash.com service uses, among others:
    1. Google Analytics services - detailed information on how Google uses data collected during the use of websites and applications of our partners is available at the address: [https://google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)
    2. Facebook services - detailed information on how Facebook utilizes collected data is available at the address: [https://www.facebook.com/business/help/560982207646475](https://www.facebook.com/business/help/560982207646475)
    3. Algolia services - detailed information on how Algolia utilizes collected data is available at the address: [www.algolia.com](https://gamerhash.com/www.algolia.com)
2. The data is collected using Cookies solely to perform specific functions for the User. The data is encrypted to prevent unauthorized access.
3. Cookies can be managed through the internet browser. Preferences can be adjusted in the browser settings:
    1. Mozilla Firefox: [http://support.mozilla.org/pl/kb/blokowanie-ciasteczek](http://support.mozilla.org/pl/kb/blokowanie-ciasteczek)
    2. Google Chrome: [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=pl&answer=95647](http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=pl&answer=95647)
    3. Internet Explorer: [http://windows.microsoft.com/pl-pl/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies](http://windows.microsoft.com/pl-pl/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies)
    4. Opera: [http://help.opera.com/Linux/9.22/pl/cookies.html](http://help.opera.com/Linux/9.22/pl/cookies.html)
    5. Safari: [http://support.apple.com/kb/ph5042](http://support.apple.com/kb/ph5042)

_Last update: 19/12/2023_

**Mobile app** Earning, HODLing and spending crypto will never be easier.

##### GamerHash

##### Help

##### See more

Site Language  

© 2024 CoinAxe sp. z o.o.

All product and company names are trademarks™ or registered® trademarks of their respective holders. Use of them does not imply any affiliation with or endorsement by them.
